“豔舞女郎”
拉斯維加斯342哩
Las Vegas 342
上車
Hop in, pard
去哪處？
Where you going?
拉斯維加斯
Vegas!
上車吧，今天你行運
Come on. This is your lucky day
願意的話，坐近點
You can sit a little closer if you want
打錯主意
Bad idea
不准胡來  知道
Chill,okay? l am chilled
有你解悶，真開心
l am glad you will be such good company
我不喜歡布祿的歌
l don't like Garth Brooks
我也不喜歡
Me, neither
有誰喜歡？
l don't know anyone who does
打算不斷亮出刀子？
You keeping that open the whole trip?
你有名字嗎？
You got a name?
我停下來，讓你下車好了
Look, l'll just pull over and you can get out
我從肯州，老遠駛來
l drove all the way from Kansas
不想好心沒好報，被人當豬宰
l ain't in the mood to get pig-stuck for doing someone a favor!  Okay?
我就把車泊去路旁
So l will just pull over
滿意了吧？
All right?
那麼…你有名字嗎？
So.. have you got a name?
我叫謝夫
l'm Jeff
娜美
Nomi
少有的名字
What kind of name is that?
我媽媽是意裔
My mom was ltalian
義大利人？
ltalian, huh?
你是黑手黨的黨徒？難怪有刀
You a Mafia girl? That's why you got your blade?
去賭城幹什麼？搏殺？
Why you going to Vegas? Going to win?
當舞蹈員
l'm going to dance
表演私人豔舞？
You going to be one of them private escort dancers?
對不起
l'm sorry. l'm sorry
拉斯維加斯：不夜天的賭城
KBlD. You never go to sleep in Vegas
賭城到了
There she is
你來過？
You been here before?
來過，叔叔是河畔酒店的接待員
Sure My uncle is a host at the Riviera
賭錢嗎？
Do you gamble?
不賭，怎贏？
Got to gamble if you want to win
我會贏
l'm going to win
用你箱子內的錢做賭本嘛
Then use that Mafia money in your suitcase
箱子留在車內吧
Leave your stuff in the car
我去找叔叔，替你介紹工作
l'll talk to my uncle. See if he can get you a job
不慣有人對你好？
Ain't anyone ever been nice to you?
玩吃角子機嗎？
Want to play a slot machine?
十元，贏的話，你我五五分賬
Here's ten bucks lf you win, we split it up
不得中飽私囊，我找叔叔去
No holding out on me either l'll go see my uncle
稍後這裡再見
l'll meet you back here
不得了！
Holy shit!
犀利！試試較大的賭注嗎？
Look at you! You want to try some silver dollars?
輸清光？想賺外快嗎？
Lose all your money, honey? Want to make some more?
只消十五分鐘就賺得到
lt won't take you any longer than fifteen minutes
遲早你都要出來做！
Sooner or later, you'll have to sell it!
媽的！
Fuck!
混帳！
Shit!
那雜種溜掉！
Fuck! The fucker left!
幹什麼？這是我的汽車！
What are you doing? That's my car!
我失去了行李！
l want my suitcase!
別碰我的汽車
Get off my car!
別理會我！
Leave me alone!
行李箱內有什麼？
So, what was in your suitcase?
沒值錢的，私人物件而已
Nothing. Just my stuff Everything l had
媽的！初到步就倒楣！
Fuck! l just got here!
歡迎光臨賭城
Welcome to Vegas
這裡有熟人嗎？
You know anyone here?
家人的電話呢？
Got any family you can call?
我沒有家人
l don't have any family
你從哪處來？
Where are you from?
東部  東部哪處？
Back east. Where back east?
東部各處！
Different places!
這樣吧
Look
要暫時棲身，可到我家
You can stay with me if you need a place to crash
地方淺窄
lt's not much
找到工作才搬走
Until you get a job
你在打我主意？
Are you hitting on me?
你不是妓女吧？
You're not a hooker?
六星期後
6 Weeks Later
安德魯另一金曲：“迎風而行”
Andrew Carver, another smash ''Walk lnto The Wind''
看！
Check it out!
好看
They're great
不俗吧？
Neat, huh?
不俗，跟我一起去嗎？
They are neat You want to come with me?
我們的舞蹈團來了個新女主角
We have this new lead She's realy good
我夠鐘上班
l have to go to work
你還有三小時才夠鐘
Jerk, you don't have to be at work for 3 hours
怎打發？看電視、吃薯片？
What will you do, watch TV and eat chips?
薯片呢？
Where are the chips?
給你吃掉？
Did you eat them?
你吃掉！   沒有
Yes, you did. You did! l didn't
你有！   停手！
You did, you did! Stop!
跟我去嘛，讓大家欣賞你的指甲
Come on, Nomi You can show off your nails
羡慕一番
They'll all be jealous
會羡慕？
You think?
我穿什麼好？
What can l wear?
穿我上星期造的裙子
Wear the dress l made last week
皺紋裙？
The fringe?
我把頭髮束起
l'll put my hair up!
沒時間束髮了
We don't have time for that
我保證會儘快
l'll hurry. l promise!
大家趕快！兩分鐘後出場！
Okay, you guys, let's go! We got two minutes!
脫外衣！
Robes off!
情形怎樣？安妮，你沒穿衣服
Ladies, how we doing? Annie, you're naked
死慕莉！
Fuck you. Molly!
什麼事？  破裂了
What happened? lt ripped
快將補好
lt's almost done
這條繩修不好，我下麵就會走光
Molly, they'll see a smiling snatch if you don't fix this G-string
我快來了，安妮
l'll be right there, Annie
她可能故意剪斷，暴露下體
She wants to smile here snatch Bet she cut the string herself
茱莉，你真刻薄，修補好
You're terrible, Julie. Okay, done
什麼味道？
What's that smell?
猴子吃大蒜後，登臺表演
The monkey act He feeds them garlic
好難聞
lt stinks
你想我無下裝登臺？
You want me onstage without a G?
我正在修補，別催，行嗎？
l'm fixing it, Annie! Give me a minute! Jesus!
誰想看她的下體？
Who'd want to see her snatch?
我就不想
l sure wouldn't
我們都知道  娜美！
We know that Nomi!
跟著來！
Come on!
列隊！四個八拍後出場，去！
Line up! You got four counts of eight. Let's go!
把花放在那處
Just set them over there
趕快！
Move it!
慕莉，我的繩褲！
Molly, my G!
巴不得她摔下樓梯吧？
Don't you wish she'd fall down the stairs?
去大堂看表演
Go watch the showroom
我可以去？
Can l go up there?
還有兩個八拍！幹什麼？快去！
You got two counts of eight! What are you doing? Let's go! Move your ass!
各位來賓…
Ladies and gentlemen
星塵隆重介紹：姬絲桃小姐
the Stardust proudly presents Miss Cristal Connors!
什麼紅星我們都請得起
We could have brought anyone into this show
麗黛積遜、蘇珊森瑪…
LaToya, Suzanne, you name it
我們選中姬絲桃
We wanted Cristal
賭城的魅力，集於她一身
Cristal Connors defines what Las Vegas is all about
光芒四射、美豔動人、十分性感
She's dazzling, exciting and she's very, very sexy
重臨本城，開心嗎？
Are you glad to be back?
對這節目有什麼看法？
How do you feel about the show?
精心製作，我希望能夠勝任
lt's the best show l've ever been in l hope l can do it justice
絕對勝任，我們萬分歡迎你
You did, and you will We're thrilled to have you here
我深感榮幸
l'm thrilled to be here
祝賀她吧
You, too
可不可以拍張獻花照片？
Can we have one of you handing Cristal the flowers?
沙克
Zack?
沙克！你去獻花
Zack! You do it
那位是娛樂總監沙克
That's Zack Carey, the entertainment director
多風度翩翩
He's so smooth
請笑納，姬小姐
Your bouquet, Miss Connors
拍照後收下，行嗎？
Can l keep them?
採訪完畢！十分感謝各位
Okay, that's it! Thank you very much for coming. Thanks
這邊來
This way, Cristal
應該送玫瑰給我
They could have gotten me roses
她多出色，對嗎？
She's great, isn't she?
不算差勁
She doesn't suck
姬絲桃找你
Molly! Cristal needs you
跟我來
Come with me
充當我的助手，來
You can be my assistant. Come on
姬小姐
Yes, Miss Connors?
叫我姬絲桃吧
Cristal, please. And you are? l'm sorry
我叫慕莉
Molly Abrams
胸圍太緊，壓扁我的乳房
This top is too tight My breasts are getting crushed
我替你放鬆
l can loosen it for you
這處放鬆點，別太松
To here, maybe. No, a little less
乳頭要罩得穩，以免波濤洶湧
l want my nipples to press, not look like they're levitating
謝謝你，親愛的
Thanks, darling
你今晚的演出很精彩，姬…小姐
You were really great tonight, Miss... Cristal
過獎
Thanks, darling
這些花是安德魯送的？
Andrew Carver sent you these?
既然咭片上是這樣寫
lf that's what the card says
我喜歡安德魯
l just love him
我朋友娜美，舞蹈藝員 是嗎？
This is my friend Nomi. She's a dancer. ls she now?
很有天份
Yes, and she's really good
在哪裡跳舞？
Where do you dance, darling?
在獵豹會所
At the Cheetah
我不知你本領多高、有什麼本領
l don't know how good you are, or what it is you're good at...
但在獵豹的話，你肯定不是跳舞
but if it's at the Cheetah, it's no dancing, l know that
你知個屁！
You don't know shit!
對不起，姬小姐
l'm sorry, Miss Connors
叫我姬絲桃
''Cristal''
已吩咐過你
l told you
姬絲桃
Cristal
你朋友的指甲不錯
Your friend has nice nails
她自己修甲
She does them herself
也許叫她替我修
Maybe she can do mine sometime
我在這裡幹活
l work here, okay?
不想惹她生氣，打破飯碗
l need my paycheck l don't want her pissed at me
對不起
l'm sorry!
離譜
Jesus, Nomi
我載你上班
l'll drive you to work, okay?
不上班
l'm not going
不怕革職？
They'll fire you
無所謂
l don't care
有所謂  無所謂
Yes, you do. No, l don't
我們去吧
Let's go
去哪裡？
Where?
還有哪裡？
You know where
她跳得不錯
She can dance, can't she?
她自以為不錯
She thinks she can
我去跟她跳
l'm gonna go dance with her
上班時間跳舞？不怕老闆？
You can't do that. You're working! T.C. will have your ass!
老闆在河畔酒店賭骰子
T.C.'s at the Riviera, playing craps
想跳舞嗎？  我在跳舞
Want to dance? l am dancing!
想跟我跳嗎？  你跳得好？
You want to dance with me? Are you good?
我跳得好
Yeah, l'm good
我買飲品去
l'm going to get a drink
你懂得跳  我沒吹牛
You can dance l don't lie
你不懂
You can't
那我在幹什麼？
Then what am l doing?
挑逗我的細佬
Teasing my dick
你有潛質，我願教你
You got potential. l could teach you
不算挑逗吧？
l'm not teasing it now, am l?
當心！
Watch it!
冷靜點
Be cool
你才去冷靜！
You be cool, buddy!
娜美！
Nomi!
抓著她！
Hey, you! Hold her!
幹什麼？
What are you doing?
是她惹起的  去死！
She started it! Fuck you!
你玩完
Party's over
娜美
Malone
你可以走
You're out of here
保釋文件
Your release papers
如何？
Yo, what's up?
我保釋你出來，咖啡也不請喝？
l bailed you out! Don't that get me a cup of coffee?
我只提議教你跳舞
All l said was l'd teach you to dance
誰要你教？
l don't need to be taught that
故此你想對我說：滾蛋，賤種！
Because you're a bad-ass, saying, ''Back off, motherfucker''
對了
You got that down
滾蛋，賤種！
Back off, motherfucker!
你害得我頭又痛、細佬又痛…
Know what? My head hurts, my dick hurts...
連飯碗也丟掉
and you got me fired from my job!
認命吧
Shit happens
“認命吧”你只贈我一句警句？
''Shit happens.'' That's what l get? Fucking wisdom?
沒有其他？  對，只有警句
That's it?! Yeah, you get wisdom
你不僅要我捱打，也要我受氣
You're not just a pain in my head and my dick, you're a pain in my ass
做人難，知嗎？
Life sucks, you know?
做人難，認命吧，T恤的標語？
''Life sucks.'' ''Shit happens'' Where you get this, off T-shirts?
我只求你請喝咖啡
All l want is a cup of coffee Yeah?
有兩毛半嗎？
You got a quarter?
自己去買一杯
Buy yourself a cup
阿爾很生氣，說你再曠工的話…
Al is pissed! He says if you miss another night...
你怎出來？  他替我保釋
How did you get out? He bailed me out
為什麼？
Why?
我踢過他祠堂
l kicked him in the nuts
他喜歡你踢？  必定喜歡
He liked it? He must have
娜美…
Nomi...
我的奶子有脹大嗎？
Nomi, do my boobs look bigger to you?
嘉米懷疑自己又懷孕
Carmi thinks she's pregnant again
你又停經？
Girl, you missed your period again?
不知道，似乎沒停過
l don't know. l don't think so
大批日本客殺到！
lt's like a Japanese convention out there!
唏，媽咪！
Hey, Mama!
準備好有味笑話沒有？
Better get your ''little weenie'' jokes ready
機關又失靈，幫幫忙
This thing ain't working again. Come on!
給我拍一拍
Here we go. Come on
加把勁，再拍一拍！
One more time. Try harder. Harder!
讓我試試
Let me try it
這位是喜望
l want you to meet Hope
規矩點，這位是蝶芬妮…
Cut it out. Hope, this is Tiffany...
花拉、希迪、亨莉…
Farrah, Heather, Henrietta...
我叫小仙，不是喜望
My name isn't Hope My name is Penny
小仙不好聽，引不起性欲
They want class They don't want to fuck a Penny
客人要操的是希迪、蝶芬妮…
They want to fuck a Heather or a Tiffany
或喜望
Or a Hope
這裡講究氣派
This is a class joint
亨莉！
Henry!
各位男嘉賓、及少數的女嘉賓…
Gentlemen, and you few ladies out there
你們期望的波後：亨莉！
what you've been waiting for Henrietta, the Queen of Bazooms!
亨莉！拉高你的裙子！
Hey, Henrietta! Pull your dress up!
你哪是我的對手？這樣多肥膏…
Honey, you couldn't handle me With all this fat...
那活寶在哪裡，你決找不到
you'd never even find the thing
我向你撒尿，你或找得到
l'd have to piss on you to give you a clue
不夠粉紅色
You need more pink
謝謝你，希迪
Thanks, Heather
跳過“坐懷舞”沒有？
Have you ever done a lap dance before?
說服客人讓你跳
You talk them into it
每趟五十元，在後房跳
Fifty bucks a pop, you do it in the back
客人眼看手勿動
Touch and go. They touch, they go
你可摸客人，客人不可摸你
You can touch them They cannot touch you
真好
That's good
胯內射精，可以
lf they come, that's okay
客人拔出來射，你叫巡場來
lf they take it out and come all over you, call the bouncer
若客人肯打賞，無關係
But if he gives you a big tip, then it's okay
明白嗎？
Got that?
你，昨晚去了哪裡？
And you. Where the fuck were you last night?
我經期到
l was having my period, Al
弄到四處是血…
You didn't want blood everywhere...
你也不想吧？
did you?
沒有一句真話，討厭
l'm getting tired of your shit
你想保住飯碗，就得向我施口技
lf you want to last longer than a week, you give me a blow job
既然受高薪，吃得鹹，要抵得渴
First l get you used to the money, then l make you swallow
他是認真的嗎？
Was he serious?
獵豹無上裝會所
Cheetah's TOPLESS LOUNGE
就是這間
Here we are
你的鼻上沾了點粉
Oh, baby...you missed a spot
那山中種田的漢子…
The farmer in the dell The farmer in the dell
竟然奪去奴家的身子
l had a cherry once, And now it's shot to hell!
下臺！下臺！
Get off the stage! Get off the stage!
你開口討人厭！我開口賺人錢！
Shut your hole, honey! Mine's making money!
在男人心目中…
Know what they call...
哪種動物只有一個器官？
that useless piece of skin around a twat?
女人！
A woman!
謝謝捧場！
That's all, folks!
各位來賓…
Ladies and gentlemen...
令你們心癢癢的希迪！
the girl to tickle your pickle! Heather!
菲臘，他說什麼？
Phil, what did he say?
他說在美國，人人都是婦科專家
He says in America, everyone's a gynecologist
你喜歡她
You like her?
我喜歡你
l like you
我替你買她私鐘
l'll buy her for you
外面有很多豪客，穿上睡袍
We got a bunch of big spenders Put your nightie on
叫他去見鬼
Tell him to go fuck himself
你敢，我趕你走
l'll kick your ass out of here
叫吧，出口氣
Tell him. Do yourself a favor
行
Okay
我穿上睡袍
l'll put my nightie on
喝杯酒嗎？
Hey! Want a drink?
我叫希迪，想看私人豔舞嗎？
l'm Heather. Would you like a private dance with me?
有奶吮嗎？
Can l suck your tits?
你不可摸我，我可摸你，好想摸
You can't touch me, but l can touch you l'd like to touch you
我有部份歡迎你摸
l know where you can touch me
什麼事？
What's going on?
他們想看她的私人豔舞
They want a private dance with her
好極，過來
So? Great. Get over there
我叫希迪
My name is Heather. Would...
娜美，我喜歡…
Hey, Nomi. l love...
你的指甲，我們想看你私人表演
your nails. We want you to have a private dance with us
只准一個客人看，女性免問
We don't do that One at a time, no women
一百元
A hundred dollars
對不起，夜總會的規矩
Sorry. That's the rule
二百！你向沙克表演，我旁觀
Two hundred! You just do Zack and l'll watch
五百
Five hundred
行
Done
我說：行
l said done
坐下來，我去更換音樂
Just sit over there and l'll change the music
什麼事？  過癮的事
What's this about? lt's about fun
你坐在那邊…
You sit there...
我坐在這邊
and l'll sit here
幹什麼？
What you doing here?
沒什麼
Nothing
想看，付錢
You want it, you pay for it
多謝
Thank you
五百元
Five hundred
夠快感嗎？
Wasn't that fun?
你存心不良
You're such a bitch
但你愛我
But you love me
走得動吧？
Can you walk?
大家晚安，回家歇歇
Good night, girls. Get some rest
去慶祝嘛
Go out. Celebrate
來我處吸大麻
Let's go to my place and smoke dope
你仍有那泰國貨？
You still got some of that Thai stuff?
我喜愛騷貨，最欣賞腿、腋部份
l love thighs. l get off on them l like armpits, too
去嗎？娜美  不去
Want to come, Nomi? Not me
我去
l'll come
你剛賺了五百元
You just got $500 off a lap dance
阿爾，別提了
Al, just stop
一副哭喪嘴臉
You act like somebody died
等一等
Wait. Listen
聽我說
Just listen
你舞蹈天份之高，我前所未見
You have more natural dancing talent than anyone l've ever seen
我在紐約拜過名師…
l've seen a lot of dancers.
見過不少人跳舞
l studied in New York. Alvin Ailey
你跳舞時，熱力逼人
You burn when you dance
你說過我不懂跳
You said l couldn't
你要學習收斂，跳舞不是性交
You have to learn to hold some in Dancing ain't fucking
又來警句？難道我不知？
ls that more Wisdom? l know that!
你昨晚像和那男人大幹特幹
You don't. You dance like when you fucked that guy last night
哪個？  有女伴那個
What guy? With the chick
在後房表演
You went in back
我沒幹他  你有
l didn't fuck him You did
你把男女都幹  你跟蹤我？
You fucked him and her. You followed me?
我沒幹過任何人！
l didn't fuck anybody!
我看見！
l saw you!
實際的性交可傳染愛滋，你呢？
Everybody got AlDS and shit What is it you think you do?
你在意識上幹他們，不妥
You fuck them without fucking them lt ain't right
你太有天份！
You got too much talent!
滾！
Get out of here!
我說的是真話！
Bitch, it's the truth!
要我走？我走好了！
You want me to go? l'm out of here!
我考到A級！
l got an A!
再上四堂課，我就有學位
Four more classes, they have to give me that degree
好極！
Great!
半年來隻靠右手自慰
l haven't gotten laid in six months
弄到右手發軟，不能執針線
My right hand's so tired, l can't thread a needle
改用左手
Use the left
用左手執針線？
For threading a needle?
好漂亮的裙子
Wow. l like that
我替你縫
l can make that
去買衣料吧
Let's go to the fabric store
我夠錢，想買
l want to buy it. l have the money
為什麼？
Why?
不知道，總之想買
l don't know. l just do
從沒有過這樣的裙子
l never had a dress like that
會很適合我
lt'll look great on me
對嗎？
Won't it?
認為如何？
What do you think?
嘩
Oh, my goodness
裙子很襯你
lt looks quite good on you
不算差勁
lt doesn't suck
我竟然買下來！
l can't believe l bought it!
我請你吃墨西哥薄餅
Come on. l'll buy you a burrito
甚至吃墨西哥火鍋也可以
l'll even buy you some...fajitas!
不行，要上早班，阿爾管得很嚴
Fuck, l can't. l'm on early Al's on my back
別擔心，我載你上班
Don't worry. l'll drive you
不得了！
Oh, my God!
他會來！
He's coming here!
你或會見到他 我應說什麼？
Maybe you can meet him! What would l say?
說：安德魯，我連針也執不起來
Say, ''Andrew, l can't even thread a needle anymore''
我兒，來娘親處！來啊！
Baby, mama's waiting for you! Come to me!
我非買入場票不可
l must get tickets for the concert!
跳多點嘛
Come on, baby
滾開！   對不起
Fuck off! Sorry
記得我嗎？
Remember me?
星塵酒店的菲臘
Phil Newkirk, Stardust Hotel
我們的舞蹈團有空缺
There's a spot open in the chorus line
明天的跳舞面試，你應該來
We're auditioning tomorrow You should try out
我？  對，你
Me? Yeah, you
你請我去試舞？
You're asking me?
我看過你跳舞，覺得你適合
When l saw you dance, l thought, Yes!''
她派你來
She sent you
沒有人派我來
Nobody sent me
十時到
Be there at ten
露個屁股來看看
l want to see your ass
我參觀你的家園，看野牛的出現
Oh, show me a home, where the buffalo roam
你參觀我的家園…
And l'll show you a home
到處是糞便！
Full of shit!
多謝
Thank you
慕莉！
Molly!
什麼事？
What is it?
我獲邀試舞！
l got an audition!
寶麗安妮！
Hey, Pollyanna!
你叫我什麼？  你像寶麗安妮
What did you call me? You look like Pollyanna
小姐們！
Okay, ladies!
我叫東尼摩士，節目監製
l'm Tony Moss. l produce this show
你們也許聽過，我是個衰人
Some of you may have heard l'm a prick
如假包換的衰人
l am a prick
我只管節目的演出…
l have one interest, and that's the show
不管你們的死活
l don't care if you live or die
我要你們能跳、能笑
l want to see you dance and l want to see you smile
你如果笑容、水準、責相不夠…
l can't use you if you can't smile, if you can't show, if you can't sell
對我沒用，現在開始檢閱
Let me take a look at you
排成一行
Spread out
有沒有搞錯？瞧這對奶子
Jesus Christ, Marty, take a look at these tits
算什麼？西瓜？
What are these, watermelons?
這是舞臺，不是果園，再見
This a stage, not a patch. See ya
我見過你
l've seen you before
我一月來面試，你叫我修理鼻子
l auditioned for you in January You told me to get my nose fixed
鼻子不錯  謝謝，摩士先生
Nose looks good. Thanks, Mr. Moss
笑容不俗
Nice smile Thanks, Mr. Moss
可惜的是，耳朵兜風
You know what, though? Your ears stick out
修理耳朵後再來
Come back after they're fixed
再見
See ya
能夠把MGM反過來讀嗎？
Can you spell MGM backwards?
MGM  佩服
M-G-M l'm impressed
把娃娃臉幹掉，再來
Come back when you've fucked this baby fat off
你的頭像網球，須戴假髮
l hope you got some wigs, tennis ball
上過什麼課程？
What classes have you had?
溜冰、芭蕾舞、爵士舞…
lce skating classes, ballet classes...
爵士舞技巧等課程
jazz classes, jazz technique classes
節目叫“女神”，不是“課程”
This show is called Goddess'''', not ''Classes.''
再見
See ya
有上過課程嗎？
What kind of classes have you had?
沒有
None
來幹什麼？
So what are you doing here?
見識你這衰人
Watching you be a prick
你還未開眼界呢
You ain't seen nothing yet
琪！示範舞步
Gay! Show them the routine
大家散開，勝出空位，先拍右腿
Everyone back up, find some space! Start with your right leg, slap it
一、二、三、四！
One, two, three, four!
五、六、七…開始跳
Go! Five, six, seven-hit it!
加把勁！
Slam it!
踢！
Kick it!
踢高！伏下！
And up! Stay down!
大家休息
Relax, you can take a break
網球頭、後面的黑髮
Tennis ball, dark hair in the back
你好，甜姐兒
Hello, doll
進展如何？   不錯
How's it going? Good
好
Okay...
你留下來
l want you to stay
還有你
And you
你也留下
You, too
再見，別枉費你我的時間，列隊
Good-bye, ladies. You wasted my time and yours! Line up!
抖出奶子來給我看
Show me your tits
這是無上裝演出，抖出奶子來！
l got a topless show! Let me see your tits!
十分不俗
Very nice
不俗，不俗
Very nice, ladies
琪！播音樂！換燈光！
Gay! Start the other music! Change the lights!
播“天使”
Cue ''Angel''
積，加強舞臺兩旁燈光！
Jack, bring up the side spots!
我要你們顯露氣勢
l want to see some attitude!
小姐們，我要氣勢！我要責相！
l said attitude! Come on, ladies! Sell!
身體的責相！
Sell your bodies!
停音樂！
Cut it!
試試練瑜伽，倒懸，再見
Try yoga, babe, or hanging from the ceiling. See ya
馬狄，冰
Marty, ice
你的乳頭有不妥嗎？
Something wrong with your nipples?
幹嗎不堅挺？弄堅挺乳頭
They're not sticking up. Stick them up
用手摸摸
Play with them a little bit
捏捏，你要的話，我願代勞
Pinch them You want me to do it for you, l'll do it
我已經堅挺
l'm erect
你幹嗎還未堅挺？
Why aren't you erect?
接著，敷冰
Here. Put ice on them
不出所料
l called that right
再見，寶麗安妮！
See ya, Pollyanna!
今日到此為止！謝謝
That's it for today! Thank you
你叫我來試舞，對嗎？
You got me the audition, didn't you?
為什麼？
Why?
也許我欣賞你的舞技
Maybe l like the way you dance
也許我欣賞你
Maybe l like you
有什麼分別？
What difference does it make?
剛才你開心了吧？
Did you enjoy that out there?
算得開心
Yeah, darling, l think l did
我恨你
l hate you
我知道
l know
抹鼻
Wipe your nose
牙醫會議的人在那邊！
The orthodontist convention is over there!
地產會議二十分後開！
Realtors come in 20 minutes!
你來幹什麼？
What are you doing here?
剛參加試舞
l just had an audition
想當舞蹈藝員？
You want to be a showgirl?
占士，快去搬行李箱！
Smith, what is this?! Move those bags!
試舞不順利？
Didn't go too good, huh?
我很高興
l'm glad
別發偉論，我沒心情聽！
Just don't, okay? l'm not in the mood!
占士，我在叫你！
Smith, l'm talking to you!
舞蹈團不適合你
You don't want to be in this kind of show
脫衣舞起碼擔白
At least what you do is honest
觀眾要看胸臀，你就露胸露臀
They want tits and ass, that's what you give
舞蹈團假充藝術，仍靠露胸露臀
Here, they pretend they want something else, you still show tits and ass
要勾搭她，用你私人時間
You want to work her, work her on your own time
我在跟她談話
l'm talking to her
我在跟她談話，並非勾搭她
l said l'm talking to her l'm not working her
你打擾我，很無禮，給我滾！
You're interrupting me and that's rude Get the fuck out of here!
賤種
Asshole
革你職！
You're fired!
拿著！
Take this!
你幹的好事，又累我丟工作
Now look what you did. You got me fired again
你的確無可藥救，不知羞
You're a real bad-ass. You got no shame
天朗氣清、陽光燦爛、財源滾滾
Look what a beautiful day it is. The sun is shining, money's flowing
我要替你解悶，請你吃超級大餐
l'm going to cheer you up. l'll get you the best meal in town
津津有味
You like that burger!
你從哪處來？
Where are you from?
從各處來
Different Places
你倒也樂意公開自己的事
You like talking about you, huh?
什麼地方？  我的家
Where are we? My place
來幹什麼？
Why?
我想給你看點東西
l want to show you something
頂級套房，我千辛萬苦才租到
Best suite in town l had to beg and plead to get it
想給我看什麼？
This what you wanted me to see?
什麼事？這張大床？
What? This nice, big bed here?
這首曲我為你而作
l wrote this number. lt's about you
你對我一無所知
You know nothing about me
我知你肯私人表演
l know you're a private dancer
湊足三個舞娘就行
l only need three other girls
我們可到殷殷會所登臺
We can put it on at the Crave Club
讓我示範
l'll show you
站在這裡看
Stand right here. Watch me
慢點！這樣嗎？
Wait a minute, slow down! Like this?
跟我跳，你跟得上
Follow me. l know you can
我有月經
l have my period
還用說
Yeah, right
摸一摸
Check
對吧？
See?
可以墊毛巾
lt's okay, l got towels
你愛我時才跟我幹
You can fuck me when you love me
那樣，我愛你！
Then l do love you!
不消說
Yeah, right
你騙不了我，我看穿你
You don't fool me. l see you
看穿什麼？
What do you see?
你有所隱瞞
l see you hiding
瞞誰？
From what?
瞞自己
From you
你有過不愉快的經歷
You got into some bad shit somewhere
謝謝漢堡包
Thanks for the hamburger!
東尼叫你立即覆電話，撥這號碼
Tony Moss called. He said to call him right away. Here's the number
打給他！好心你，我打
Call him! Oh, Jesus. l'll call him
我叫娜美，想找東尼
Tony Moss, please. lt's Nomi Malone
錄用了我
l got it
這德州黃玫瑰，每趟五十元收費
She's the yellow rose of Texas, she charges 50 bucks
她發的大財，都靠床上苦幹得來
She's the richest girl in Texas, and all she does is fucks!
你遲到 不會再到，另有工作
You're late. l'm gone. l got another job
改投另一間會所？
Where? You going to another club?
有更高的分賬？我照付
You getting a better cut? l'll match it
我去參加星塵的“女神”演出
l'm in ''Goddess'', at the Stardust
有什麼好笑？
What's so fucking funny?
她轉投星塵，參加舞蹈演出
She's going down to the Stardust! She's in the show
可喜可賀
Well, good for her!
她會回來
She'll be back
我決不回來！
No, l won't. l'll never come back!
你是脫衣舞娘，怎不自量？
You're a stripper. Don't you get it?
我是舞蹈員！
l'm a dancer!
你是舞蹈員，亨莉就是聖母！
lf you're a dancer, Henry here's the Virgin Mary!
比起聖母，我更大胸、更多口！
l got bigger tits than the Virgin Mary, and a bigger mouth, too!
唯有你能替我修理那露乳機關
Damn it. You're the only one who gets my tits popping right
再見，阿爾
See ya, Al!
我不會再雇用你
l'm not hiring you back, hear me?
即使你為我吹簫！
Not even if you give me a fucking blow job!
占士！
James!
開門！
Come on!
我已被錄用！
l got it!
參加“女神”演出
l'm in the show! ln ''Goddess''
我為你作的曲呢？
What about the number l wrote?
還以為我們會合作
l thought we were working on something
占士
James?
你也為她作曲？
She's in your number?
等一等！
l'll be right there!
她不懂跳舞
She can't dance
但你會教她，對嗎？
But you'll teach her, right?
她有天份，對嗎？
She's got talent, right?
你我間沒有瓜葛
You and me, we ain't got no ties
跳舞不是性交，對嗎？
Dancing ain't fucking. Right?
對…
Yeah...that's right
再見
See ya
那是誰？
Who was that?
想合作跳舞的人
Someone who wanted to be in the number
你不會用她取代我吧？
You're not giving her my part, are you?
不會，她不懂跳舞
Nah, baby. She can't dance
那首曲我為你而作
l wrote that number for you, you know that
對不起
Excuse me
什麼貴幹？
Can l help you?
我叫娜美，來見摩士先生
l'm here to see Mr. Moss Nomi Malone
可以進去
Okay. Go on in
她那天看似倔強的寶麗安妮…
One day she looks like Pollyanna
今天看似誘人的羅烈蒂
the next she looks like l don't know, Lolita
不俗的裙子
Nice dress
我在華茜買的
Thanks. l bought it at Ver-sayce
富林商場
ln the Forum?
對了，我喜歡華茜
Oh, yeah, Ver-sayce. l love Ver-sayce
我也是
Me, too
你認識馬狄吧
Okay, you know Marty
琪是領隊
Gay is our line captain
我這超級衰人的聲譽，得來不易
lf you let me down, l'll lose reputation for being an all-knowing prick
別教我失望，令我聲譽受損
l worked very hard for that reputation, so don't do it.
同意嗎？
Deal?
同意
Deal
琪會介紹情形
Gay will show you around
跟我來
Let's go
娜美，我們今午練舞
Nomi? We'll do a run-through this afternoon
祝你好運
Good luck
賭場贏你錢前，先祝你好運
They tell you that here just before taking your money
你得保持身材，吃赤米、蔬菜
You must maintain your weight Eat brown rice and vegetables
避開陽光，以免曬成兩截色
And stay indoors Tan lines aren't allowed
化妝服飾由你保管，不得帶回家
Make-up and costumes are your responsibility. Don't take them home
千萬不要在臺上哭泣
And don't ever, ever go out onstage crying
你吃赤米、蔬菜吧？
You do eat brown rice and vegetables, don't you?
好
Good
你的化妝台
This is your table
你像我那樣理智的話…
lf you're smart, and l was smart...
為自己的事業、物件，及早鋪路
you'll figure out a job and man for later on
你怎找到對象？
How'd you find your guy?
我補牙時，結識了那牙醫
l chipped my tooth on a Quaalude He was my dentist
你每晚上落樓梯六次
You'll run this monster 6 times a night
緊握扶手，我帶你去人事部
Hold onto the railing. l'll take you to personnel
人事部要資料
They want some information
什麼資料？
What kind of information?
出生日期
Date of birth
七三年七月三日
1973/7/3
出生地點
Place of birth
紐約
New York
紐約市？
New York, New York?
親人
Nearest family members
無親無故
l don't have family
都去世？
Deceased?
是
Yes
曾被捕？有案底？
Have you ever been arrested? Charged with a criminal offense?
沒有
No
福利證件號碼？
Social Security number
不知道，待我查出後，告訴你
l don't know Let me check on that for you, okay?
你受錄用！好極！
You got it! Nice going!
沙克，這位是娜美
That's great. Zack, this is Nomi Malone
我記得，你好
l remember her. Hi
你當然記得
l bet you do
相當難忘，歡迎加入，漂亮的裙
She's pretty memorable. l'm glad you're part of the team. Nice dress
華茜的時裝
lt's a Ver-sayce
“華莎姿”
lt's Versace
應該讀作“華莎姿”
lt's Versace. lt's pronounced Ver-sa-chee
你夠品味、夠美貌
You have a great taste. You look beautiful
小姐們！
Girls!
這位是娜美
This is Nomi!
妮奇、茱莉、甸娜，琪你已認識
Nicky, Julie, Deena and you know Gay
她們示範，你旁觀
They'll run through it. You watch
吃過東西沒有？
Did you eat?
積！吃什麼？
Jack! What do you want?
漢堡、薯條、梳打
Burger, fries and soda
替她買赤米、蔬菜、礦泉水
Get her some brown rice, vegetables and an Evian
不，先看示範
No, Nomi, come take a look at this
準備！五、六、七、八！
Here we go! Five, six, seven, eight!
輪到你，準備…
You try it now. Ready?
五、六、七，開始！
Go! Five, six, seven, hit it!
踢！加把勁！
Kick it! Work it!
停！那是什麼轉身？
Hold it! Nomi, what kind of turn was that?
足尖旋轉，轉吧
Do a pique turn. Come on
對了，音樂！
That's it. Okay, music!
來吧！
Go! Hah! Go!
高點
Higher
不要那樣高
Not that high
配合音樂節奏！
Stay in sync!
一，二，三，一
One, two, three, one!
挺！挺！
Thrust it! Thrust it!
Thrust it! Come on!
夠了，謝謝各位
Okay! That's enough. Thank you, ladies
幹得好
Good job
要她多練轉身，留意身體平衡
Work on her turns. l'm worried about her balance
我幾時開始表演？
How long before l can do the show?
今晚開始
You start tonight
今晚？  你應付得來
Tonight? You'll be fine
她的表現如何？
How did she do?
並非花拳繡腿
She's no butterfly
腰有挺勁，渾身野性
She's all pelvic thrust. She prowls. She's got it
哪處來的野性？
l wonder how she got it?
不是學來的
She didn't learn it
是學來的，但並非從課堂學來
She learned it, but it's not taught in any class
多點橙色，我替你塗
You need more orange. Let me do it
覺得怎樣？
How do you feel?
不要問！
Don't ask. Don't ask!
我的化妝品呢？
Who took my make-up?
猩猩來了！
Monkey alert! Monkey alert!
早叫你看管猩猩！
Damn it, Hector! l told you!
猩猩春情動，要生孩子！
They get the heat! They make babies!
孩子？
Babies?
趕出去
Oh, get it out
小心
Watch it
走！   抓著那猩猩！
Go! Go! Grab her!
我抓著一頭！
Hey! l got one!
其餘在樓上
The rest are upstairs
淫婦，不准再碰我的化妝品！
Julie, you slut, don't touch my make-up!
淫婦？你操那送外賣的小子！
l'm a slut? You fucked that pizza place kid!
你操那抄表漢子！
You fucked the meter reader!
潑貨！   你活得不耐煩
Bitch! You're fucking dead!
安妮，停手
Jesus, Annie, get off her!
茱莉，冷靜點
Julie! Calm down! Stop it!
打架到此為止
Now settle down! lt's done!
夠鐘演出
Showtime
去！四個八拍！
Move! You got four counts of eight!
等一等，假髮
Nomi, wait. Your wig
你應付得來，大家上去！
You're fine. Let's move up, you guys!
舞臺上有糞便
There's shit on the stage
猩猩吃完蒜頭總拉糞
They always shit. lt's that garlic
糞便在哪？  左後邊
Where? Top left
左後舞臺有猩猩糞，去！
Upstage left, monkey shit. Let's go!
吸點可卡因嗎？
Want some blow?
敷冰的最後機會
Last chance for ice
快！
Let's go!
快！快！
Go, go, go, go!
我愛你
l love you
大家快點！娜美，跑！
Come on, you guys, keep it moving! Run, Nomi!
等一等！
Nomi, wait!
第二拍，一、二…去！
Two beats. One, two...go!
媽的
Shit
各位，星塵隆重介紹姬絲桃小姐
Ladies and gentlemen, the Stardust presents Miss Cristal Connors
有兩分鐘，戴上紅發，我取服裝
You got two mins. Put on your red wig l'll get your costume
祝順利，沙克
Good luck. Love, Zack Carey
娜美，穿上去
Nomi. Slip this on
我表現如何？   好
Did l do okay? You did fine
伸腿須改善，明天中午來練舞
Your leg extension needs work. Someone will work with you. Be here at noon
戴上去，行
Put this on. You're done
我沒摔倒  差點摔倒
l didn't fall. You nearly fell
喂！
Hey, yo!
談談行嗎？
Can l talk to you a minute?
求求你
Come on, please?
談吧
Talk
單獨談
Alone?
我去開車  我很快來
l'll get the car. Be right there
誰送的花？
Who sent you the flowers?
不關你事
None of your business
我只想說…
Okay. l just wanted to say...
你我間沒有瓜葛
You and me ain't got no ties
我承認好色
l have a problem with pussy
一向如此，改不了
l always have, and l always will
但我言出由衷
But l meant what l said
我才不管 那首曲確為你而作
l don't care about your problems. l did write it for you
但我答應過教她，也搞上她
But l did tell her l would teach her, and l did fuck her
你搞上誰是你的事，不關我事
Who you fuck is your business l won't make it mine
那首曲既然賺不了錢…
lt's not like l'm seeing any money for writing that number
我順便用來泡女人
l may as well touch a little pussy
你沒話說？
You got nothing to say
是
No
謝謝你的花
Thanks for the flowers!
東尼贊你跳得好
Tony said you did great!
我從沒接過花
l never got flowers before
我肯定陸續有來
l'm sure you'll get lots of them
他送的花？
He gave them to you?
對
Yeah, he did
幹什麼職業？扯皮條？
What is he? A pimp?
那是部扯皮條型的汽車
Only people with pimp cars are pimps
他是娛樂總監
He's the entertainment director
果然是扯皮條
That's what l said. He's a pimp!
我們走吧
Let's go!
祝你好運
Good luck with your number
喂
Hello?
有人嗎？
Anybody here?
觀眾席這裡
Back here
你來幹什麼？
What are you doing here?
我來幹什麼？
What am l doing here?
來吸世間最好的可卡因，要嗎？
Doing some of the finest cocaine in the world. Want some?
舒筋活絡妙品
lt's great for the muscles
我對馬狄說，會教你轉身…
l told Marty l'd work on turns with you...
但現在有點不舒服
but l'm feeling a little inside-out
廢話少說
Cut the shit
好吧
Okay
你我一直有點誤會
We got off on the wrong foot
不記前嫌，和解如何？
Want to start dancing all over again?
為什麼和解？
Why?
為什麼不和解？
Why not?
去史柏高吃午餐嗎？
Want to go eat at Spago?
在哪裡？
Where is it?
在華茜附近
Just down from Ver-sayce
華莎姿
Versace
對，華莎姿
Ahh, right. Versace
請享用
Enjoy
什麼東西？
What is all this stuff?
我替你點菜
l'll order for you
我要赤米、蔬菜
l'll have brown rice and vegetables
你喜歡赤米、蔬菜？
Do you like brown rice and vegetables?
喜歡吃？
You do?
可算喜歡
Sort of
真的？
Really?
比狗糧難吃
lt's worse than dog food
的確難吃
lt is
我吃過狗糧
l've had dog food
你吃過？
You have?
好久以前
A long time ago
狗餅
Doggy chow
我以前喜歡吃狗餅
l used to love Doggy Chow
我也是
l used to love Doggy Chow, too
喝香檳我會頭痛
l got a headache from champagne
這不是香檳
This isn't champagne
是姬絲桃牌聖水
This is holy water
我藝名的出處
l named myself after this holy water
我原本叫姬絲，褐發、小乳房
Chrissie Lou Connors had dingy brown hair and little tits
化妝、隆胸後，脫胎換骨
lt's amazing what paint and a surgeon can do
你的整容一流
You have great tits
養眼
They're beautiful
過獎
Thank you
我欣賞美觀的乳房
l like nice tits
一向都欣賞，你呢？
l always have. What about you?
我喜歡有美觀的乳房
l like having nice tits
你愛怎樣包裝？
How do you like having them?
什麼意思？
What do you mean?
你明白我的意思
You know what l mean
我愛穿漂亮的裙子…
l like having them in a nice dress...
或緊身上衣
or a tight top
你喜歡露胸
You like to show them off
我不喜歡在獵豹露
l didn't like showing them at the Cheetah
為什麼？
Why not?
我跟所有觀眾一樣欣賞
l liked looking at them there. Everybody did
我覺得像娼妓
lt made me feel like a hooker
你是娼妓啊
You are a whore, darling
我不是
l'm not!
我們都是
We all are
我們賺錢，全靠迎合觀眾的愛好
We take the cash, we cash the check, we show them what they want to see
也許你是娼妓，我不是
Maybe you're a whore, but l'm not
你與我…
You and me...
都是同一種人
we're exactly alike
我怎也不會似你
l'll never be like you
姬小姐，麻煩你簽個名，行嗎？
Miss Connors! Sorry to bother you Would you sign this for me?
樂意，大名是什麼？
Happy to. What's your name?
法蘭，來自德州
Frank. l'm from Galveston
我也是德州人
l'm from Del Rio myself, Frank
我早說過她是德州人，瞧！
l told you she was from Texas. Whoo-ee, look at that!
也替我簽，行嗎？
Could l have one like that?
你不想印幹我的口紅吧？
You want a girl to use up all her lipstick on you?
想跳舞嗎？   現在跳？
Want to dance? Right now?
正如貓王那首歌：“機不可失”
lt's now or never. That's what Elvis said
我聽過句金石良言…
You know the best advice l ever got?
你渴望得到一個舞臺空缺…
You're up there onstage, hoping on a spot
不妨把所有對手，逐個踩下臺
lf someone gets in your way, step on them
最後剩下你，空缺非你莫屬
lf you're the only one left standing there, they hire you
我想說的已說完，謝謝
That's about it. Thank you and good night
到此為止
Elvis has left the building
親愛的，看吧…
You see, darling...
你是娼妓
you are a whore
賤人！
Bitch!
大概已鬧翻
Guess we're done
妮奇，我有話跟你說
Nicky, can l talk to you for a second?
媽，看猴子行嗎？  現在不行
Mommy, can we see the monkeys? Not now
求求你  猴子要工作
Please. They're so cute. They have to work
什麼工作？
What are they doing?
我要看猴子！   現在不行
l want to see the monkeys! Not now
為什麼？
Why not?
趕他媽的小孩出去
Get these fucking kids out of here
你說粗口！她說粗口
You said the F'' word! She said the ''F'' word''
她說粗口
She said the F'' word!''
他媽的閉嘴！
Shut the fuck up!
不要怕
lt's okay. lt's okay
下星期本城舉行遊艇展覽會
Nomi, a boat convention's coming into town next week
要兩位小姐，妮奇願去
They need two girls. Nicky's doing it
你呢？工資一千元
You interested? lt pays $1,000
一千元？幹什麼？
A thousand dollars? To do what?
替酒店宣傳，花枝招展地拍照
Represent the hotel. You wear your costume, smile, they take your picture
一千元？
A thousand dollars?
好極，姬絲桃推薦你
Great. Cristal here recommended you
謝謝
Thanks
別客氣，我總會關照你
My pleasure, darling. Just looking out for you
雜誌的特寫… 稍後才理會
Cristal, about the magazine layout...? Later
不要幹
Don't do it
一千元，為什麼不幹？
lt's $1,000. Why not?
慕莉，來！
Molly, l need you!
來了，幹過的小姐都不…
l'm coming. l know girls who did it and they...
慕莉，我在等著！
Molly, l'm waiting
她們都不高興
They didn't like it
你幹過沒有？
Did you do it before?
喜歡嗎？
Did you like it?
我喜歡嗎？喜歡啊
Did l like it? Sure, l liked it
兩位在女神中演出的佳麗，謝謝
Let's thank these 2 beautiful girls from Goddess'', a new smash at the Stardust''
倒楣
Shit
情況怎樣？   好
How's it going? Fine
苦差，對嗎？
Tough gig, huh?
對極
Very
我的老友，曼谷來的興田先生
This is my good friend, Mr. Okida, from Bangkok
他是我們賭場的大豪客
He's one of our very, very high rollers
表演完後，肯賞面一同進餐嗎？
Ladies, we want to take you to dinner after the show
吃龍蝦，聽凱撒唱歌
Have some lobster, hear Caesar sing
聽過凱撒唱歌嗎？保證悅耳
You ever heard Caesar sing? The guy's great. You'll love him
凱撒唱歌？
Caesar sing?
然後回我家，我們也唱歌
Then we'll go back to my place and we'll sing
只有我們四人唱
Just the four of us
如何？
How about it?
我們唱歌
We sing
對，大展歌喉
Yeah, we'll sing a lot of songs
行
Okay
好極
Good deal
好，好極
Okay. Good deal
恕不奉陪
Not me
識趣點嘛  放手！
Be nice. Let go of me!
這差事有一千元
You got $1,000 for this
對，這展覽會！
Yeah, for this! This!
算了
Oh, forget it
生什麼氣？沒碰過你一根頭髮！
Just forget it! No harm done! No damage!
哼！
Christ!
沙克
Zack?
我想跟你談談
l want to talk to you
上樓去吧
Let's go upstairs
今日開心嗎？
Have a nice day, darling?
不
No
可惜
l'm sorry to hear that
離譜
Jesus
對不起，有些人真不知所謂
l'm sorry. Some people just don't get it
我在臺上，叫菲臘來
l'm on the stage. Get me Phil
謝謝
Thank you
不要走開
Stay
吃角子機進賬增33%
The drop is up 33% on those machines
即是說，每部進賬250元歸本
lt will make your bottom line about 250
我?這工作獲MBA
l got an MBA for this
現在注重的是，成本分析
That's what this business is now cost analyzing slot machines
MBA是什麼？
What's an MBA?
沙克，你在嗎？
Zack, you in here?
失陪
Excuse me
唏！什麼事？
Hey! What's going on?
再有下趟，你另謀高就
You do anything like this again, you're fired
什麼也沒發生  還強辯？
Nothing happened. Something did!
她未搞清楚就亂跳
She jumped to conclusions
下趟，輪到你跳：請你跳槽
lt happens again, you'll jump to your conclusion
休想有遣散費
Without your golden parachute
還不向她道歉？
You owe her an apology
娜美，對不起
Nomi, l'm sorry. l apologize
好吧
Yeah, fine. Okay
滾
Get out
MBA是工管碩士，沒實際用場
An MBA is a college degree. lt's mostly worthless in the real world
你雄心勃勃
You go for it, don't you?
我盡力而為
Yeah, l try to
夠鐘演出
Showtime
的確
That's for sure
菲臘你這飯桶，回來
Phil, you dumb fuck, get back up here
知道、知道
l know, l know
謝謝你的關照，向菲臘推薦我
Thank you for looking out for me. You were so nice to recommend me to Phil
我們是朋友嘛
What are friends for?
對
Right
展覽會的事，你說得對
You were right about the convention
甜姐兒
Sweet baby!
你再摸，我扭斷你的手指！
Do that again, l'll break your fingers!
沒法，只有我對異性有興趣
Not my fault you don't have a gay partner
操你
Fuck you
他拼命宣傳自己是異性戀
He wants everyone to see how hetero he is
拿電筒照照他的行頭多大
Molly, bring that flashlight so l can see how big it is
想吃老拳嗎？
You want a knuckle sandwich?
我用後門吃，行嗎？
Can l have mine anally, please?
別吵了！離譜
Come on, you guys! Jesus!
列隊準備！
Let's go! Let's line it up!
望什麼？賤人
What you looking at, bitch?
快點！去！
Okay, let's go. Move it! Go, go, go!
糟糕
Oh, my God
傷了哪處？安妮
Are you okay, Annie?
我的腿
lt's my leg
哪處痛？
Tell me when it hurts
她的膝蓋
lt's her knee
碎了，對嗎？
lt isn't broken, is it?
什麼回事？
Daryl, what happened?
我一時腳滑
My foot went out from under me
是這一回事
This is what happened
怎會在舞臺上出現？
l wonder how those got up here?
或許從服飾脫落
Probably came off a costume
我們送你入院
We'll get you to the hospital
好痛
Shit, no!
可憐的安妮，多倒楣
Jesus. Poor Annie. Tough break
請挪開
Let us through here
稍後見
See you later
我是監製
l'm the producer
你是我雇員，聽我命令
l hired you! You do what l say
安妮是我的候補，我有發言權
She was my understudy. l have a say, too
但決策權不在你處
Yeah, but guess who makes the decision
她的膝蓋碎了
lt's broken, kids
慘，要三個月才復原
Shit. That will be three months
起碼
At least
報應
Bad karma, huh?
娜美，你媽媽在等你
Nomi, your mother's waiting for you
我的媽媽？
My mother?
為你著想，我希望她不是
For your sake, l hope she's not
醒睡的人易睡醒…
lf a light sleeper sleeps with a light on
挺硬的人可硬挺？
Can a hard sleeper sleep with a hard on?
雌老虎哪處厲害？兩個吃人的口
What do you call a tiger? A big pussy that eats people
亨莉！
Henry!
吻出口水，好過噴出口水
l can get shit on, but l don't like getting spit on
阿爾
Hi, Al
你難看極
You look like shit
十吋陽具也不及她好看
She looks better than a 10-inch dick and you know it
在這裡…工作開心嗎？
So...do you like it here?
難道她會懷念你？
What, you think she misses you?
有什麼稀奇？
Yeah, why not?
我們懷念她
We miss her
她懷念我們，像我懷念我那痔瘡
She misses us like that lump on my twat l had taken off last week
離譜
Jesus, Henry
我們看過你演出
We saw the show
你跳得精彩
You were good
謝謝你，阿爾
Thank you, Al
的確精彩
Real good
保重，小姑娘
You take care, kid
你沒有引死人，著實奇怪
Must be weird, not having anyone come on you
娜美，要我載嗎？
Nomi. Hey, you want a ride?
我已有人載
l got one
等一等！
Wait!
坐過這汽車嗎？
Ever been in one of these?
不
No
我夢寐以求的事
l always wanted one
不同凡響吧？   不算差勁
lt's some car, huh? lt doesn't suck
往哪處去？你帶路
Where are we headed? Give me directions
往你家去
To your place
你愛喝姬絲桃香檳？
Do you like Cristal?
我愛喝各種香檳
l like a lot of different champagnes
但我只喝香檳
But l always drink champagne
安德魯是怎樣的人？
What's Andrew Carver like?
你緊張？毋須緊張
Are you nervous? Don't be
我沒有緊張
l'm not
我喜歡你的高潮
l liked it when you came
喜歡你的眼睛
l liked your eyes
留下來
Stay with me
早上我載你回去
l'll drive you back in the morning
現在是早上
lt is morning
請留下來
Please?
我已叫計程車
l have a taxi coming
取消好了
Send it back
姬絲桃要位新候補
Cristal needs a new understudy
中午試舞，可有興趣？
There's an audition at noon. You want to try?
我不來這裡，你會告訴我嗎？
Would you have told me if l hadn't come here?
提議來的是你，不是我
lt was your idea to come here, not mine
我想再見你
l want to see you again
看情形才說
We'll see how it goes
看什麼情形？試舞？
What, the audition?
十元半
Ten-fifty
喂！
Hello!
恨死你
l hate you
對方是誰？   沙克
Who was he? Zack
還得了
Oh, my God
有沒有縛起他？
Did you tie him up?
慘
Oh, shit
我忘記解開他
l forgot to untie him
吸毒吸醉了？
Are you high?
有點
Maybe a little
不能睡，中午要試舞，麥片呢？
l can't go to sleep. l have an audition at noon. Where are the Sugar Snaps?
在櫃裡，娜美…
ln the cupboard. Nomi...
不要上毒癮
don't get sucked into it
看我找到什麼！
Look what l found!
隨便你好了
Okay, whatever, Nomes
我選茱莉
Julie
她不夠性感  她舞步熟練
She's not hot enough. She has it down
但沒有姬絲桃的熱力
You can teach it. She doesn't have Cristal's heat
誰也沒有
None of them have Cristal's heat
教我怎不愛你
l do love you, Gay
娜美有熱力
Nomi has heat
有嗎？
Does she?
娜美有
Yes, she does
完全不同的熱力
ln a totally different way
說笑！由她當主角？
Come on! She's going to take the lead?
這是大型節目，不是脫衣舞！
This a hotel show! lt's not the Cheetah!
不要緊，八年來我從未失場
lt doesn't matter l haven't missed a show in 8 years
你不會愈來愈年輕
You're not getting any younger
狗種
Eat me
看娜美試舞嗎？  不
Want to see it again with just Nomi? No
我看，去準備吧
l do. Set it up, Marty
不知所謂
This is bullshit
假公濟私
lt's about your dick
妮奇、茱莉，謝謝
Nicky, Julie, thank you!
有她的資料嗎？
What do we know about her?
全無，連福利證號碼也不可靠
Nothing. l doubt her Social Security number's right
調查她   查什麼？
Find out. What?
一切
Everything
你與她有一手？
You fucked her, didn't you?
你生氣，因為妒忌？抑或…
Are you pissed off because you're jealous?
因為被我捷足先登？
Or because l beat you to the punch?
你操他，為空缺？抑或為興趣？
You fuck him for the spot or because you wanted to?
我相信，你為空缺
l say you did it for the spot
你慣用身體作交易？
ls that what you did, Cristal?
我們既是朋友，激怒我對你無益
You don't want to piss me off, now that we're friends
你不應動怒
No, you shouldn't get pissed off
動怒令你衰老
lt makes you look older
你升為候補
You got it
真的？
l do?
馬狄與琪會教你
Marty and Gay will work with you
菲臘會安排宣傳，你幹得好
Phil will have some glossies taken. You did good
我們一起進餐、吃龍蝦
l'll call you for dinner, lobster
聽過凱撒唱歌嗎？保證悅耳
Did you ever hear Caesar sing? You'll love it
望什麼？
What?
恭喜，原來你多才多藝
Congratulations. l see you have many talents
我認為她跳得好
l thought she did good
殷殷會所 占士舞蹈演出
A Private Dance By James Smith The Crave Club
事後我才知道試舞的事
l didn't know about the audition until afterwards
我的指甲怎樣？
Do you like my nails?
比不上你的漂亮
They're not as nice as yours
也許有空我替你修甲
Maybe l'll help you with yours sometime
你願意的話
lf you want
你真好人
lsn't that nice of you, darling?
我們是朋友嘛
What are friends for?
想深一層…
On second thought...
也許不應讓你修甲
maybe you shouldn't do mine
我太老，不適合婊子打扮
l'm getting too old for that whory look
我會考慮一下
l'll think about it
出去時關門
Close the door on your way out
不懂跳舞，不要假充！
Hey, bring on the real dancers!
噓！
Boo!
差勁！
You suck!
下臺！
Get off the stage!
表演夠了！
Enough of this stuff!
我們跳舞吧！
Let's dance!
好看、出色
l loved it! lt was good
你來，不怕失身份？
What are you doing here, slumming?
希迪！
Heather!
我們怎樣？
Were we good?
好極
Great
她跳得笨手笨腳
She dances like a truck!
怎會！要喝東西嗎？
l do not! Do you want something to drink?
來杯啤酒，婆娘
Yeah. Get me a beer, bitch
看我的戒指
Look what l got
真美
lt's beautiful
我從祖母處偷來
l stole it from my grandmother
不是！你從當鋪處買
You did not! You got it at a pawnshop
我們快結婚
We're getting married
你愛她？
You love her?
不知道，奉子成婚
l don't know. She's having a baby
演出呢？
And this?
不受歡迎，觀眾喝倒采
We ain't any good. You heard them. ''Get off the stage!''
有什麼打算？
What will you do?
幫外母打理雜貨店
Work in a grocery store Her mother owns it
嬰兒食物我們有折扣
We'll get a discount on baby food
再見
See ya
認命吧、做人難，對我用得上
Shit happens, you know? Life sucks. l'm a student of T-shirts!
妮奇
Hey, Nicky
娜美小姐…
Dear Ms. Malone,
我們不能選你為後補…萬分遺憾
We regret we are unable to offer you...understudy
不准進去！
You can't go in there!
什麼事？
What's going on?
“什麼事？”
What's going on?!
冷靜點   “冷靜點”！
Hey, cool it. Cool it?!
竟發這封信來！
When you sent me this?!
她用離職威脅，出動律師
She threatened to walk! She got her lawyers into it!
又如何？
So what?!
她是個明星！你及不上
So, she's a star! You're not worth it
對不起，娜美，我已盡力
Sorry, Nomi. l tried. Fuck!
繩胯斷掉，我赤裸裸跳足五分鐘
Basically, my G-string snapped. There l was, dancing butt naked for 5 mins
難為了我的舞伴
l mean, my poor partner!
我考慮過，親愛的
l thought about it, darling
現在替我修甲，行嗎？
Think you could do my nails now?
行
Okay
或許改天吧
Maybe some other time
隨我來…女奴隸
Come on...slave girl
五分鐘後出場，快！
We've got five minutes. Go!
大家趕快！
Go, you guys! Run, run!
讓路！
Let me through!
慘！
Shit!
姬絲桃，你聽見我嗎？
Cristal, can you hear me?
叫馬狄來！
Somebody get Marty!
什麼事？   不知道
What happened? l don't know
召救傷車！
Somebody get an ambulance!
誰在她後面？
Who was behind her?
我
l was
發生什麼事？
What happened?
不知道，她突然摔下去
l don't know. She just went down
滑倒，我看到
She slipped. l saw it
娜美離她很遠
Nomi wasn't even close to her
多倒楣
Tough break, huh?
什麼事？
What's wrong?
沒什麼
Nothing
謝謝，有消息請通知我
Thanks. Keep me informed
她腦部受震盪，無大礙
She has a concussion. That'll be all right
但臀部嚴重斷骨
But she has a compound fracture of the hip
康復極費時日
Those take forever to heal
必須關閉
We have to shut down
無論如何得表演下去
Not a chance. The show goes on
星塵是不夜天，從沒試過關閉
The Stardust is never dark. lt has never been
只要我活著，決不關閉
lt never will be. Not while l am alive
誰是後補？
Who was her understudy?
我們有位小姐…
We had a girl who...
笑什麼？
What's funny?
姬絲桃是位明星，無可取代
Cristal Connors is a star, Sam! You can't just replace her
我們聘人暫代，等她康復
We could bring someone in while she's out
可能要等一年
She could be out for a year
聘誰？
Like who?
珍納積遜、寶拉阿都
Janet Jackson. Paula Abdul
上我的節目？
Paula Abdul? ln my show?
酬金過巨，我們付不起
We're not paying those kind of salaries
既然如此，我們依照賭城作風…
ln that case, Mr. Karlman, we do what we do in Vegas
博一博
We gamble
各位來賓
Ladies and gentlemen...
星塵鄭重介紹：娜美小姐
the Stardust proudly presents Miss Nomi Malone
我們誰也雇得起
We could have hired anyone
珍納積遜、寶拉阿都
Janet Jackson, Paula Abdul
賭城的魅力，集於娜美一身
Nomi Malone is what Las Vegas is all about
她光芒四射、美豔動人…
She's dazzling, she's exciting...
十分性感，謝謝你，沙克
...and very, very sexy. Thank you, Zack
覺得今晚的演出怎樣？
How did you feel about the show tonight?
我希望能夠勝任
l hope l can be as good as the show
你勝任有餘，本節目全靠你
You are, my dear. You are the show
望過來，娜美
Good one. Over here, Nomi
再來一張！麻煩你
One more, Nomi! Please, please
有派對，準備好未？
Hey, you ready to party?
哪裡？  我租下天堂酒店
Where? The Paradiso. l rented the bungalows
為誰開？   為你
For what? For you
快，豪華房車接送
Hurry. l got a limo waiting
我沒有適合的衣服  你有
l don't have anything to wear! Yes, you do
安德魯也去，他欣賞你的演出
Andrew Carvers' coming He saw the show and thinks you're great
聽到嗎？安德魯也會去！
Did you hear? Andrew Carver will be there!
聽到了
Yeah. l heard
什麼事？
What's wrong with you?
你推她下去
You pushed her, didn't you?
沒有
No
你怎可這樣說？茱莉見到
How can you say that to me? Julie saw it
不可能，她當時背向你，我在場
She couldn't have seen it. l saw Julie and her back was to you
她見到
She saw it
算了
Okay
祝你派對開心
Have fun at your party
去嘛，不去怎行？安德魯也去
Come here, Molly! You have to come Andrew will be there
我不管
l don't care
沒你，派對沒意思
lt ain't a party without you
放手
Let go of me
放手！
Let go of me!
獻給這世上獨一無二的美女！
To the one and only beautiful girl in the world
等一等
One minute
犀利
Oh, my God
我想知道的是…
So, what l want to know is...
安德魯在哪裡？
where's Andrew?
看
Look
女神娜美
Nomi Malone Goddess
真羡慕你的打扮
l love your outfit
娜美…我可以做你的候補嗎？
Nomi... you think l could be your understudy?
我會考慮
l'll see what l can do
謝謝你
Thanks, darling
安德魯到了，我來介紹
Andrew Carver's here. l want to introduce you
安德魯到了！
Andrew's here!
安德魯…娜美
Andrew Carver...Nomi Malone
精彩的演出
You were sensational tonight
過獎  哪裡
Thank you. And you're welcome
在哪處發掘她？
Where did you find her?
軍事秘密
l'll never tell
我喜歡你的歌
l like your songs
我喜歡你的屁股，打電話給我
And l like your ass. Call me
慕莉…
Molly Abrams...
安德魯
Andrew Carver
我連針也執不起來
l can't even thread a needle anymore
什麼？
Sorry?
慕莉是你的忠實歌迷
Molly's one of your biggest fans
既然如此…我替你倒杯酒
Well, then...let me get you a drink
隨我來
Come on
玩得開心點
Enjoy
你今日多美
You look beautiful tonight
什麼事？
What's going on?
耍樂一下
Just want to party, baby
放手！
Let me go!
抓住她
Get her!
放手！   他媽的閉嘴！
Let me go! Shut the fuck up!
扔她上床！
Throw her down!
幹她！
Fuck her!
幹她吧！
Fuck her, man
幹她！
Fuck her! Fuck her!
放開我！
Let me go!
幹她！
Fuck her!
我可能愛上你
l could fall in love with you
我們走吧
Let's get out of here
慕莉
Molly?
她受驚過度，已注射鎮定劑
We have her sedated. She's in shock
鼻樑折斷、陰道破裂
She has a broken nose, vaginal tears
要留醫三、四日
She'll be here three or four days
沙克！
Zack!
看這個
Look at this
還有這個，稍後見
And look at this. Later
員警呢？   不會來
Where are the police? They're not here
為什麼？   不來就不來
Why not? Because they're not coming!
不要報警…
Don't do it...
寶麗
Polly
你怎知道？
How did you find out?
你曾在殷殷會所被捕
You were busted at a fight at the Crave Club
警方有你指紋
The police took your fingerprints
我不想聽
l won't listen to this
不由你不聽！
Yes, you will!
你叫寶麗安！
You're Polly Ann Costello!
父親殺死母親後自殺！
Your father killed your mother, then killed himself!
你被收養，一九九零年出走
You ran away from a foster home in Oakland in 1990!
案底：科州責淫…  別說！
Arrests: Denver, soliciting... Stop it!
加州、懷州賣淫！讀下去好嗎？
San Jose, Cheyenne, soliciting! Shall l read the rest?
藏可卡因、持械行兇
Possession of crack cocaine! Assault with a deadly weapon!
為什麼不繼續當娼？
Tell me something. Why did you stop hooking?
你反正已確定人生路向
You had your future pretty well mapped out
我不得已
l did what l had to do
就像你對付姬絲桃？
Just like you did with Cristal
我不是娼妓
l'm not a whore
你不是
No...you're not
你會成為紅星
You're going to be a big star
街上掛著你的大型海報
Your face will be up on billboards
你會替星塵賺大錢
And you will make a lot of money for the Stardust
你放過安德魯？
You'd let him get away with this?
他今年在天堂酒店演唱
Andrew Carver is at the Paradiso this year
明年或在星塵
He might be at the Stardust next year
他是自己人，你也是
He's part of the team. So are you
慕莉呢？
What about Molly?
他會賠錢，慕莉可開時裝店
l'll see he gives her enough money to have a dress shop
告訴我
Tell me something
你收費多少？
What did you charge?
賣淫的收費
Hooking
五十元，有時一百元
Fifty. A hundred sometimes
自貶身價，你的功夫著實一流
You got low self-esteem, baby. You're a fantastic fuck
我在讚賞你啊
l was paying you a compliment
夠鐘演出
Showtime
安德魯，麻煩你
Andrew Carver, please
打扮得好
Hello, baby. Looking good
他在等候你
He's ready for you
你來得快
lt didn't take you long
我喜歡你無上裝
l like you better topless
等一等我無下裝
Wait till you see me bottomless
我正在等
l'm waiting
統統脫掉
Take the rest off
得
Sure
你出聲，我捅死你！
You make a sound, l'll fucking kill you!
好
Okay, okay
賤種！
Fucker! Fuck off!
別打擾，他想睡覺
He says he wants to sleep
筋疲力竭
Tired him out, huh?
藥物關係，她仍未清醒
She's still out. lt's the medication
她平安嗎？
ls she okay?
平安
She's okay
慕莉
Molly?
我剛去找過安德魯…
l just went to Carver...
把他踢得不似人形
and kicked the shit out of him
我愛你
l love you
請問姬絲桃在哪？  319號房
Cristal Connors, please. Room 319
記得我的金石良言嗎？
You know the best advice l ever gave you?
最後剩下你的話…
lf you're the only one left standing...
那空缺非你莫屬
they'll hire you
謝謝來賓，晚安
Thank you and good night, ladies and gentlemen
到此為止
Cristal has left the building
對不起，姬絲桃
l'm sorry, Cristal
我明白你多內疚
Yeah. l know just how sorry you are
我當上主角，也使同一手段
How do you think l got my first lead?
總會有人更年輕、更野心…
There's always someone younger and hungrier...
跟著你下樓梯
coming down the stairs after you
為什麼不說我推你？
Why didn't you tell anyone?
親愛的…我需要歇一歇
Oh, hell, darling...l needed a rest
況且，我也獲得一大筆賠款
Besides, my lawyers got me a real nice settlement
我要走了
l have to go
不給我來個熱吻？
Aren't you going to give me a big kiss?
再見，親愛的
Bye, darling
上車！快點！
Come on! Hurry up!
上來吧，今天算你走運
Hop in, pard This here is your lucky day
出發
Let's go
有博一博嗎？
So did you gamble?
贏？
Did you win?
贏了什麼？
What did you win?
贏回自己
Me
媽的
Oh, fuck
是你
lt's you
還我的行李箱來！賤種！
l want my fucking suitcase, asshole!
我正在駕駛啊！離譜！
l'm driving! Jesus fucking Christ!
留意交通！
Watch the fucking road!
還你行李箱好了
Be cool! l'll get your suitcase.
誤會而已，別衝動
lt was a mistake. Mellow out!
女神娜美
NOMl MALONE lS GODDESS